Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - correspondence: Lloyd Richards (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Nina Riegger (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: David Rintels (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Roach (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Earl Robinson (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Rockafeller Foundation (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Rockafeller Foundation - Italy (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Rogers and Cowan (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Rolling Repertory (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - info: Peter Brook, director (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - info: British American Arts Association's National Theatre World Felllowship program (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - "Bristol Old Vic", playbill (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - info:Brandeis Uni. awards (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - info: John Brademas (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Ray Bradbury (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - misc. items (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: John Bos (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Vera Borkovec (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - info on a David Boorstein article, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Richard Block (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - recommendation to NYU for Kim Bey (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Michael Bertin (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Norman Bernstein (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Paul Berman (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - info: Michael Bertin (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - info: Black Theatre (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - publication, "Black Masks" (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - black history month (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - recommendation for Allie Bird (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Livingston Biddle (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Black Theatre (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Susan Smith Blackburn Contest (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Doug Wager (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - correspondence: Fritz Brun (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - info: Robert Brunstein (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Richard Bryant (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - info on Budapest (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Budapest Conference (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Budapest / Paris trip (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Bulandra (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Bulgarian Embassy (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Cynthia Burns (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Red Burns (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Vinie Burrows (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Ellen Burstyn (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - business committee for the arts (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Cable TV conference - June 1981 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Peggy Cooper Cafritz (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - California Contacts (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Judson camp (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Canadian Embassy (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corp. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - cancer - medical info (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - The Canterbury Hotel (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - correspondence: Arthur Cantor (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Jose Cantu (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - subscriber capacity chart, 1974-1988 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - correspondence: Capital Rep (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - correspondence: Al Carmines (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - correspondence: Earle R. Gister (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Liviu Ciulei (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Liviu Ciulei (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Liviu Civlei (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Liviu Ciulei (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Harold Clurman (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - The Cleveland Playhouse (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Ricky Cluchey (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Ricky Cluchey (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - casting information (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - The National Theatre of Norway, brochure (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The National Theatre of Norway, correspondence and information (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - info and draft of the Arena Stage storey (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Herman Obermayr, "52 Weeks of One Man's Opinion" (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: The Honorable Sandra Day O'Connor, Associate Justice of the Supreme Court (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - resume and photos of Thomas O'Connor (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - NEA information (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - correspondence and info: NYU program (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - info: Zelda become head of acting/directing program at NYU (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence and script for " The Great Whale Chase" (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: NYU (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: David Oppenhiem (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - NYU commencement programs, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - brochures for the graduate acting program at NYU (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - misc. information on NYU acting program (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - New York Theatre Workshop (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: The Actors fund (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - trip to Norway, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - misc. notes and correspondence (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - info on the 1968 playwrights conference (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - research, J. Oppenheimer (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Zsuzs Orkeny (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Sally Ourieff (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - misc. info and map of Paris (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Paramount Hotel (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - misc. materials (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: National Choral Foundation (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Suzanne Weil (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Peace Child Foundation (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Richard Peaslee (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: University of North Carolina (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - "Once in Doubt", playbill, correspondence and misc. material (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - program: Summerfare, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Performing Arts Journal (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Performing Arts Journal (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - brochure: The Performers Ensemble (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: The Pew Charitable Trust (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Philadelphia Bar Associations, playwrighters competition (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Philadelphia Festival Theatre, program (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - "Wanted", playbill, correspondence, information (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - "Waiting for Godot", playbill, reviews and misc. materials (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - " A Walk in the Woods", reviews, correspondence (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - "The Wall", script, notes, correspondence (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - "Watch on the Rhine", script, set design plans, correspondence (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - "What the Babe Said" and " Total Recall", scripts (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - "What the Babe Said" and " Total Recall", scripts (cont.) (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - brochure, Theatre Cabaret (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - "Way of Life", correspondence (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - "What the Butler Saw", playbill, misc. materials (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - "We Wont Pay!", playbill (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - "West Memphis Mojo", playbill (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - "What the Butler Saw", production material (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - The Arena Adventure, formate typepages for for the 1980's (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - highlights 1974-1975 season (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - The Arena Adventure: The Russia Tour, draft (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - The Arena Adventure: choronological highlights, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurb on 1972-1973 seasoon (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurb on 1971-1972 season (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1970-1971 season (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - The Arena Adventure: living stage highlights (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - The Arena Adventure: the 1970's (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - The Arena Adventure: introduction draft (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - The Arena Adventure: a season for all audiences (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - The Arena Adventure: the 1980's (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronology (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1973-1974 season (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1974-1975 season (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1975-1976 season (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - The Arena Adventure: The Tony Award (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - The Arena Adventure: in the process (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1976-1977 season (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1977-1978 season (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - The Arena Adventure: The Eastern European Connection (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1978-1979 season (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1979-1980 season (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - The Arena Adventure: the new building (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - The Arena Adventure: highlights 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1961-1962 season (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs 1963-1964 season (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - The Arena Adventure: highlights, 1965-1966 season (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1967-1968 season (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - The Arena Adventure: highlights, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1968-1969 season (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1968 three play repertory essay (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - The Arena Adventure: highlights, 1969-1970 season (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1969-1970 season (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - The Arena Adventure: living stage essay (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - The Arena Adventure: The Great White Hope, essay (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - The Arena Adventure: The Great White Hope, Essay (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - The Arena Adventure: preface to the book (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - The Arena Adventure: staging of the arena (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - The Arena Adventure: forward to the book (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1950-1951 (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1951-1952 season (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - The Arena Adventure: additional chronology, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1956-1957 season (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1953-1954 season (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1954-1955 season (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - The Arena Adventure: the acting company (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - The Arena Adventure: blurbs, 1956-1957 season (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - The Arena Adventure: funding (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - The Arena Adventure: proof of "arena staging" (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - The Arena Adventure: proof of "Arena Staging" (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - The Arena Adventure: institutional pages (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronologocal highlgihts, 1958-1959 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronological highlights, 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronology, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - The Arena Adventure: highlights, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronology, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1980's essay (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - The Arena Adventure: special productions (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - The Arena Adventure: cultural diversity (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronology, 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - The Arena Adventure: Merrily We Roll Along (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - The Arena Adventure: execution of justice (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - The Arena Adventure: the acting company (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - The Arena Adventure: tribute to Alan Schneider (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1960's essay (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1980's essay (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1980-1981 season production list (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - The Arena Adventure: chronology, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - The Arena Adventure: Galileo (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1981-1982 season production list (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - The Arena Adventure: correspondence on corrections of the 1980's (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1981-1982 season chronology (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1981-192 season highlights (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - The Arena Adventure: K2 essay (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1982-1983 season list (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1982-1983 chronology (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1982-1983 season highlights (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1983-19984 season production list (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1983-1984 season chronology (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1983-1984 season highlights (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - The Arena Adventure: special productions (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1984-1985 season production list (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1984-1985 season chronology (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1984-1985 season highlights (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1985-1986 season production list (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1985-1986 season chronology (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1985-1986 season highlights (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1986-1987 season production list (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1986-1987 season chronology (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1986-1987 highlights (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - The Arena Adventure: Marx Brothers essay (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1987-1988 season production list (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - 1987-1988 season chronology (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1987-1988 highlights (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1988-1989 season production list (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1988-1989 season chronology (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1988-1989 highlights (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - The Arena Adventure: cultural diversity essay (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1989-1990 season production list (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - The Arena Adventure: 1989-1990 season highlights (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - The Arena Adventure: cultural diversity essay (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - The Arena Adventure: old vat seating chart (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - The Arena Adventure: the arena adventure the first 40 years (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - The Arena Adventure: archival material (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - The Arena Adventure: letter to Edward Mangum (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - The Arena Adventure: art work negatives (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - The Arena Adventure: (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - the Commonweath Award program, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - "The Bo'suns in search of a Berth", press release (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - SS Potomac (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - "The Passing of a Queen", the SS Potomac Storey (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - news clipping on ground breaking of the new building (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - SS Potomac, outline (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - a timeline of the Arena Stage (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - news clipping of the "Miser" (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - "The Ruling Class", playbill (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - program, the arena stage storey (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - artical on Arena Stage (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - 1950-1970, first 20 years manuscript (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - archiving books (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - artical on Arena Stage (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - brochure for Arena Stage's 30th (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - artical on Zelda (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - publishers place artical on Zelda (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Arena Stage's production history sheet (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Christian Science Monitor artical (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Washingon Post artical on Zelda, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - playbill for 1982-1983 season Gala Opening (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - photos from the 1950's (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - "Androcles and the Lion", playbill (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - "The Caucasian Chalk Circle", playbill (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - misc. news clippings on arena stage (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - case statement for the Arena Stage endowment campaign, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Arena Survey: study of operations (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Arena Board of Trustees (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Arena Employees season breakdown (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage premieres (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Announcement, May 16th (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Arena Stage endownment campaign: misc files (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Arena endownment campaign: misc. files (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Arena endownment campaign: misc. files (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - The Back Alley Theatre (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - James Backas, applicant for executive director (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Peter John Bailey; playwright (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Arthur Ballet; University of Minnesota (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Julie Watson Barbour; playwright (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Barbwire Theatre inc. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Pina Bausch; actress (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Brooks Atkinson (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - misc. audience response letters (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - The Directos Voice program (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Bartow interview of Zelda (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - artical on Phillip Barry (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - letter of recommendation for B.H. Barry (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Clive Barnes (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - artical on Alan Ayckbourn (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Avignone Festival (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - misc. audience response letters (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - misc. audience response letters (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Bob Benedetti (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Beate Hein Bennett (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Ned Beatty (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - correspondence and info: Eric Bently (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Melia Bensussen (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Ivan Berend (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Arena Posters (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - audience surveys (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - playlab archives (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - marketing study- shugoll research (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Herbet Berghof (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - artical on Ingrid Bergman (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Berkeley Repertory Theatre (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Albert Berkowitz (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Arena Stage handbook, first edition (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Arena Stage Premieres (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: John Arnone (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Aronld Aronson (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - artistic home chapter (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - artistic director plight (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - arts pac (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - correspondence: Association for Theatre Education (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Assitej/USA theatre (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - ASTI (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - George Mason University: archive project (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: George Wasshington University (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Budapest magazine artical on Zelda (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Norman Gevantor (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Tony Giardina (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Alfred Gingold (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Arthur Giron (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Earle Gister (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Susan Gitenstein (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: David Glenn (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - correspondence and info: John Glore (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Resume: Magret Glover (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: James Godfrey (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Peter Golub (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Mordecai Gorelik (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Women in Theatre (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Don and Mary Graham (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - info and artical: Martha Graham (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Andre Gregory (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Trevor Griffiths (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Charles Gross (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - correspondence: Grotowski (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Guthrie Theatre (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - correspondence: Clara Gyorgyey (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - correspondence: John Guare (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - correspondence: Peter Hackett (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - correspondence: John Houseman (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - articals: Allen Hughes (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Jaques Huisman: National Theatre of Belgium (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - The Huntington Theatre Company (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Lester Hyman (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - research: Ibsen (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - report from the Independent Committee on Arts Policy (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Ted Hoffman-NYU (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Benita Hoistetter (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Barbara Hogenson (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Gitta Honegger (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Horizons Theatre (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Israel Horovitz (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Horvath (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Helen Hayes, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - info: Armand Hammer (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: mark hammer (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Dorothea Hammond (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Julie Harris (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Father Hartke (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Pat Mathis Harrey (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Frank Hauser (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Vaclav Havel (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Alex Hawkins (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - correspondence and info: Helen Hayes (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - the Helen Hayes Awards, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Hadassah's Myrtle award, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Uta Hagen (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Charlie Haid (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Martin Halpern (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Edward T. Hambleton (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Helen Hayes Awards (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - articals: Sally Jane Heit (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Donald Hense, resume (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Lunch for Patrick Hayes (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Haymarket Theatre (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Suzanne Heard (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Hebrew Academy Award, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Hedgerow Theatre - gail cohen- (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Michael Heim (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Robert Herridge (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Hippocrates Oath (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: John Hirsch (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - The Historical Society of D.C. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - costume memos - misc. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - "creativity" (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Lou Criss (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Michael Cristofer (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Hume Cronyn and Jessica Tandy (Box 72, Folder 5)